Configure Flutter settings.

To remove a setting, configure it to an empty string.

The Flutter tool anonymously reports feature usage statistics and basic crash reports to help improve Flutter tools over time. See Google's privacy policy: https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/

Global options:
-h, --help                  Print this usage information.
-v, --verbose               Noisy logging, including all shell commands executed.
                            If used with "--help", shows hidden options. If used with "flutter doctor", shows additional diagnostic information. (Use "-vv" to force verbose logging in those cases.)
-d, --device-id             Target device id or name (prefixes allowed).
    --version               Reports the version of this tool.
    --enable-analytics      Enable telemetry reporting each time a flutter or dart command runs.
    --disable-analytics     Disable telemetry reporting each time a flutter or dart command runs, until it is re-enabled.
    --suppress-analytics    Suppress analytics reporting for the current CLI invocation.

Usage: flutter config [arguments]
-h, --help                                 Print this usage information.
    --list                                 List all settings and their current values.
    --clear-ios-signing-settings           Clear the saved development certificate or provisioning profile choice used to sign apps for iOS device deployment.
    --select-ios-signing-settings          Complete prompt to select and save code signing settings used to sign apps for iOS device deployment.
    --android-sdk                          The Android SDK directory.
    --android-studio-dir                   The Android Studio installation directory. If unset, flutter will search for valid installations at well-known locations.
    --jdk-dir                              The Java Development Kit (JDK) installation directory. If unset, flutter will search for one in the following order:
                                               1) the JDK bundled with the latest installation of Android Studio,
                                               2) the JDK found at the directory found in the JAVA_HOME environment variable, and
                                               3) the directory containing the java binary found in the user's path.
    --build-dir=<out/>                     The relative path to override a projects build directory.
    --[no-]enable-web                      Enable or disable Flutter for web.
                                           (defaults to on)
    --[no-]enable-linux-desktop            Enable or disable support for desktop on Linux.
                                           (defaults to on)
    --[no-]enable-macos-desktop            Enable or disable support for desktop on macOS.
                                           (defaults to on)
    --[no-]enable-windows-desktop          Enable or disable support for desktop on Windows.
                                           (defaults to on)
    --[no-]enable-android                  Enable or disable Flutter for Android.
                                           (defaults to on)
    --[no-]enable-ios                      Enable or disable Flutter for iOS.
                                           (defaults to on)
    --[no-]enable-fuchsia                  Enable or disable Flutter for Fuchsia.
                                           This setting applies only to the master channel.
    --[no-]enable-custom-devices           Enable or disable early support for custom device types.
    --[no-]cli-animations                  Enable or disable animations in the command line interface.
                                           (defaults to on)
    --[no-]enable-native-assets            Enable or disable native assets compilation and bundling.
                                           (defaults to on)
    --[no-]enable-dart-data-assets         Enable or disable Dart data assets building and bundling.
                                           This setting applies only to the master channel.
    --[no-]enable-swift-package-manager    Enable or disable support for Swift Package Manager for iOS and macOS.
    --[no-]omit-legacy-version-file        Enable or disable stops writing the legacy version file. If set, the file {FLUTTER_ROOT}/version is no longer written as part of the flutter tool execution; a newer file format has existed for some time in {FLUTTER_ROOT}/bin/cache/flutter.version.json.
                                           (defaults to on)
    --[no-]enable-windowing                Enable or disable support for windowing on macOS, Linux, and Windows.
                                           This setting applies only to the master channel.
    --[no-]enable-lldb-debugging           Enable or disable support for debugging with LLDB for physical iOS devices. If LLDB debugging is off, Xcode debugging is used instead. Only available for iOS 17 or newer devices. Requires Xcode 26 or greater.
                                           (defaults to on)
    --[no-]enable-uiscene-migration        Enable or disable support for migrating to UIScene lifecycle. If enabled, Flutter will migrate your app to iOS UIScene lifecycle if possible or otherwise instruct you to migrate manually.
    --clear-features                       Remove all configured features and restore them to the default values.

Run "flutter help" to see global options.

Analytics reporting is currently enabled.
